{
    "subject": "resource/University_of_Ostrava",
    "predicate": "property/name",
    "object": "University of Ostrava",
    "human_readable": "The name of University of Ostrava is University of Ostrava.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9329332113265991,
            "question": "What type of institution is the University of Ostrava?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8631092309951782,
            "question": "Where is the University of Ostrava located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8060822486877441,
            "question": "Is there a sports team associated with the University of Ostrava?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7748844027519226,
            "question": "What are some popular majors offered at the University of Ostrava?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6886706352233887,
            "question": "Does the University of Ostrava have a notable alumni network?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.38907507061958313,
            "question": "What is the full name of the University?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3781100809574127,
            "question": "Is there another name by which the University is known?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.27985310554504395,
            "question": "Does this university have a nickname?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.10587669163942337,
            "question": "What is the university's motto?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.08271331340074539,
            "question": "Does the university offer undergraduate and graduate programs?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The name of University of Ostrava is University of Ostrava.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2803_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the university's motto?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2803_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does this university have a nickname?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2803_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there another name by which the University is known?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2803_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2803_100.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2803_101.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2803_104.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2803_129.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2803_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2803_139.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2803_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2803_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2803_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2803_76.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents does support the triple that the name of the University of Ostrava is indeed the University of Ostrava. This is explicitly stated in all four documents provided, as shown below.\n\n* Document 101.txt: \"The University of Ostrava (UO)...\"\n* Document 100.txt: \"The University of Ostrava (UO)...\"\n* Document 31.txt: \"The University of Ostrava is an essential part of the city and its social life...\"\n* Document 5.txt: \"The University of Ostrava (UO)...\""
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about the University of Ostrava, confirming that its official name is indeed \"University of Ostrava.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}